http://www.lumenera.com/corporate/legal.html

Home ProductsOEM & CustomIndustrial & ScientificMicroscopySurveillanceAstroUSB 3 CamerasUnder DevelopmentWhere to Buy SupportIndustrial (USB & Ethernet)Drivers & DownloadsTraining & TutorialsUSB FAQsEthernet FAQsInstallation & Power GuidesApplication NotesProduct Modification NoticesMicroscopyDrivers & DownloadsTraining & TutorialsFAQsInstallation & Power GuidesApplication NotesProduct Modification NoticesSurveillance (Ethernet)Drivers & DownloadsFAQsInstallation & Power GuidesApplication NotesProduct Modification NoticesAstro (USB)Drivers & DownloadsFAQsInstallation & Power GuidesApplication NotesProduct Modification NoticesAbout Technical SupportKnowledge BaseContact TACTAC UpdateRMATake Back and Recycle ProgramWarranty Information News & EventsEventsIn the NewsPress ReleasesPress Release ArchiveNewslettersNewsletter Sign Up ResourcesCase StudiesBrochuresSample Image/VideoIndustrialMicroscopySurveillanceAstroLumenera TVLogos and GuidelinesAssociations Corporate About Lumenera Contact Us Submit Feedback Management Team CareersWhy Lumenera Financial Overview Community SupportGreen Program PartnersTechnology PartnersBecome a Partner Blog Events Corporate News Did you Know Industry News Items of Interest Products Specs and Techs
Home Corporate LegalLegalLumenera Corporation (Lumenera) makes available information, materials, and products on this website, subject to the following terms and conditions. By accessing this site, you agree to the terms and conditions as outlined in this legal notice. Lumenera reserves the right to change these terms and conditions from time to time at its sole discretion.CopyrightThe information on this website is protected by copyright: Copyright ©2018 Lumenera Corporation. All Rights Reserved. Except as specifically permitted herein, no portion of the information on this website may be reproduced in any form or by any means without prior written permission from Lumenera.Use of Website InformationExcept as otherwise indicated elsewhere on this site, you may view, copy, print, and distribute documents available on this website subject to the following conditions:The document may be used solely for personal, informational, non-commercial purposes;The document may not be modified or altered in any way;Any copy of the document or portion thereof must include the copyright notice above and this permission notice; andLumenera reserves the right to revoke such authorization at any time, and any such use shall be discontinued immediately upon written notice from Lumenera.Documents specified above do not include the design or layout of this website. Elements of this website are protected by trade dress and other laws and may not be copied or imitated in whole or in part.Warranties and DisclaimersEXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY PROVIDED OTHERWISE IN AN AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND LUMENERA, ALL MATERIAL ON THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY OTHER WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABLE QUALITY, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR THOSE ARISING BY LAW, STATUTE, USAGE OF TRADE, OR COURSE OF DEALING. LUMENERA ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE INFORMATION OR OTHER DOCUMENTS WHICH ARE REFERENCED BY OR LINKED TO THIS WEBSITE.REFERENCES TO CORPORATIONS, THEIR SERVICES AND PRODUCTS, ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. IN NO EVENT SHALL LUMENERA BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER OR NOT ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGE, AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS INFORMATION. SOME STATES/COUNTRIES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.THIS WEBSITE COULD INCLUDE TECHNICAL OR OTHER INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY ADDED TO THE INFORMATION HEREIN; THESE CHANGES WILL BE INCORPORATED IN NEW EDITIONS OF THIS WEBSITE. LUMENERA MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THE PRODUCT(S) AND/OR THE PROGRAM(S) DESCRIBED IN THIS WEBSITE AT ANY TIME.Confidential Information; PrivacyUnless otherwise explicitly stated herein or in the Privacy Policy, any non-personal information or material sent to Lumenera will be deemed NOT to be confidential. By sending Lumenera any non-personal information or material, you grant Lumenera an unrestricted, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, display, perform, modify, transmit and distribute those materials or information, and you also agree that Lumenera is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques that you send us for any purpose. However, we will not release your name or otherwise publicize the fact that you submitted materials or other information to us unless: (a) you grant us permission to do so; (b) we first notify you that the materials or other information you submit to a particular part of a site will be published or otherwise used with your name on it; or (c) we are required to do so by law.To learn more about how Lumenera protects your personal information, such as your name and address, please refer to the Lumenera Privacy Statement.Links to Third-Party WebsitesThe Lumenera website might contain links to third-party websites, which are not under the control of Lumenera. Lumenera makes no representations whatsoever about any other website to which you may have access through the Lumenera website. When you access a non-Lumenera website, you do so at your own risk and Lumenera is not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any information, data, opinions, advice, or statements made on these sites.Lumenera provides these links merely as a convenience and the inclusion of such links does not imply that Lumenera endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content or uses of such websites.Governing Law and JurisdictionThis website (excluding linked sites) is controlled by Lumenera from its offices within the Province of Ontario, Canada. By accessing this website, you and Lumenera agree that all matters relating to your access to, or use of, this website shall be governed by the statutes and laws of the Province of Ontario, without regard to the conflicts of laws principles thereof. You and Lumenera also agree and hereby submit to the exclusive personal jurisdiction and venue of the courts of the Province of Ontario with respect to such matters. Lumenera makes no representation that materials on this website are appropriate or available for use in other locations, and accessing them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access this site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws.Trademark InformationThe trademarks, logos and service marks ("Marks") displayed on this website are the property of Lumenera or other third parties. You are not permitted to use the Marks without the prior written consent of Lumenera or such third party, which may own the Marks. "Lumenera" is a registered trademark of Lumenera Corporation.
video title video content
